The last guy she wants is the only one she needs.
Drive Me Crazy is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by John Schultz.
Nicole and Chase live next door to each other but are worlds apart.
However, they plot a scheme to date each other in order to attract the
interest and jealousy of their respective romantic prey.
But in the mist of planning a gala centennial celebration, Nicole and Chase find
that the one they always wanted was closer than they ever thought.
Nicole Maris, played by Melissa Joan Hart.
Chase Hammond, played by Adrian Grenier.
Alicia DeGasario, played by Susan May Pratt.
Ray Neelay, played by Kris Park.
Dulcie, played by Ali Larter.
David Ednasi, played by Mark Webber.
Drive Me Crazy is a 1999 American teen romantic comedy film based on the
novel How I Created My Perfect Prom Date by Todd Strasser.
Originally entitled Next to You, the film's title was changed to Drive Me Crazy after one
of the songs from its soundtrack, "(You Drive Me) Crazy" by Britney Spears.
The film received mixed reviews and grossed $22.6 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of high school, prom, next door neighbor.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.